http://adventurerabbi.com/privacy-policy/

DonateContactJoin Our NewsletterMembershipMy Account
HomeEducationAdventure Rabbi Kids (Alternative Outdoor Religious School)Online Adventure Rabbi KidsARK InternsHebrew TutoringHebrew Tutor – Ari SharfsteinHebrew Tutor – Jason LansingHebrew Tutor Janiece GratchHebrew Tutoring Rabbi JamieHebrew Tutor David SpieglerHebrew Tutor Shana WebbHebrew Tutor – Zoë Wilhelmsen (she/her)Hebrew Prayers VideosAdult Education and Bar & Bat MitzvahPrivate Study with Rabbi Jamie KorngoldIntroduction to JudaismBring Adventure Rabbi to Your Congregation or GroupBar & Bat Mitzvah (Alternative)Endorsements of Our ProgramResources for Bar Mitzvah and Bat Mitzvah FamiliesBar Mitzvah & Bat Mitzvah DocumentsBar
Yisrael & Bat Yisrael DocumentsHebrew Prayers VideosAdventure B’nai Mitzvah Class Schedule 2020-2021Suggested Locations for CeremoniesVendors We LoveDesign Your Own Silk TallisCeremony Set up Diagram and PhotosHebrew TutorsOnline Bar Mitzvah/ Bat Mitzvah Class With Rabbi JamieAdventure Bar Mitzvah & Bat Mitzvah ClassAdult Education and/or Adult Bar & Bat MitzvahBar & Bat Yisrael (alternative Bar Mitzvah)Destination Bar Mitzvah / Bat Mitzvah ServiceDistance
Bar Mitzvah LearningIndividual
and Online Bar Bat MitzvahIsrael Bar Mitzvah / Bat Mitzvah ServiceMitzvah Bar Mitzvah & Bat Mitzvah ClassNon-Hebrew Bar Mitzvah
OptionLife-CycleBaby NamingBris / CircumcisionBar & Bat Mitzvah Alternatives : Online, In-person, Class or IndividualConversionFuneral ServicesPremarital CounselingWeddingsJewish CouplesInterfaith CouplesKetubahRenewal of VowsHoliday RetreatsPassover in MoabRosh Hashanah During COVID-19Yom Kippur During COVID-19Downloads Needed for High Holiday ServicesEvent Photo GalleryShabbatFridays on FlagstaffMapShabbat on Snow at CopperHebrew Prayers VideosKidsAdventure Rabbi Kids (Alternative Outdoor Religious School)Online Adventure Rabbi KidsARK InternsAdventure Rabbi TeensOutdoor AdventuresSukkot HikeFind Us OutsideHike with the RabbiRabbinic House CallsRemember When…Virtual Shabbat Fridays at 6 pm MTShabbat in Person Summer 2020Virtual Seder 4/8/2020 at 5 pmPassover In IsraelCamp Adventure Rabbi KidsFamily Thanksgiving in Israel 2015Guide-TrainingJewish Education for Military FamiliesAspen to Crested Butte Hike 2013Spiritual Ski Trips with Rabbi Jamie KorngoldAdult LearningAdventure for ages for 20s 30sYom Kippur Boulder, CORosh Hashanah at Camp Granite LakeAboutAbout Adventure RabbiBoard of TrusteesContact Me NowEndorsementsEvent CalendarFranchiseFree Mezuzah ScrollJob PostingsMembershipPress & NewsPress KitRabbi Jamie Korngold’s BlogOrders
Privacy PolicyPrivacy Promise & Privacy Policy:Privacy PromiseAdventure Rabbi, Inc. is dedicated to helping develop vibrant Jewish experiences in the outdoors. We take privacy very seriously, and we’ve taken many steps to help safeguard your online information. We promise you that:We will safeguard any information you share with us.We will not share information you provide us without your permission.We will not send unsolicited e-mails.You can unsubscribe from our email mailing list at any time.We continuously assess ourselves to ensure that your privacy is respected. Please read our Privacy Policy below for more information.Privacy PolicyWhen you visit www.adventurerabbi.org, we will not collect any personally-identifiable information about you unless you decide to provide information to us. If you decide to request more information from us, or sign up for a seminar or our email newsletter, for example, we will ask you to provide information such as your name, email address, phone number, and other additional information so that we can respond to your request. You are not required to provide this information, however the services we can offer you may be limited without it. We use this information solely as required to respond to your particular request and to improve both the usability of our site and our user support procedures. The Adventure Rabbi, Inc. Web site also automatically logs visitors’ IP addresses and Internet Service Providers (“ISPs”); and may record information such as confirmation email messages sent, opened, delivered and clicked through. Adventure Rabbi may also record information to help prevent the misuse of our system.Consent:At Adventure Rabbi, Inc., we believe that our visitors own their personal information. We will always give our registrants a choice regarding how the personally identifiable information they provide us may be used. Our registrants will always have the opportunity to opt in or out of any data collection or distribution.Disclosure:Adventure Rabbi, Inc. will not willfully share the personally-identifiable information collected from our visitors (i.e. registrants) without their consent. The only exception to this policy is when we are required to do so by a legal statute, a law enforcement agency, or regulatory authority. This will usually be done only after we receive a court order or subpoena that requires us to release information.In certain cases, an emergency request from a verifiable law enforcement agency may be honored prior to receiving a court order or subpoena. We will make every reasonable effort to notify our registrants as soon as possible if we receive a request for the release of information so that our registrants can have the opportunity to pursue any legal rights and remedies they may have under the law.Under certain circumstances, a court order or law may prohibit us from notifying our registrants of a request for information. Examples of this include cases in which fraud and/or criminal activity is suspected. In these cases, we will make every effort to notify our registrant, at the earliest possible time permissible under the law.Adventure Rabbi, Inc. occasionally sends outbound administrative email communications to ensure that our registrants are aware of significant updates or changes to the company. We encourage you to allow us to send this information to you so that you will always be aware of the latest information about Adventure Rabbi, Inc..We respect your right not to receive any email that you have not specifically agreed to receive and, in furtherance of this right, have put policies in place that allow our registrants to control the delivery of these messages, or to prevent delivery if that is your preference.In some cases Adventure Rabbi, Inc. must send administrative emails to our registrants to alert them to specific changes that may impact their ability to use a service they have previously signed up for, regardless of their email contact opt-in status. We also reserve the right to contact you if compelled to do so as part of a legal proceeding.Adventure Rabbi, Inc. reserves the right to change its privacy policy to reflect new services that help further establish innovative customer-centric products and services. Notifications of changes to our privacy policy will occur by posting of a message on Adventure Rabbi, Inc. web site at www.AdventureRabbi.org or by users voluntarily viewing the privacy policy for periodic changes. In addition, the Privacy Policy link will always contain the most up-to-date Policy so that our registrants will always have the most current information about our disclosure principles regarding their data and about how Adventure Rabbi, Inc. will manage registrant information.Data Security:At Adventure Rabbi, Inc., we employ security techniques and well-defined employee practices to ensure that data is protected from unauthorized access and use. We hold our employees accountable for maintaining the privacy and integrity of our registrants’ information. We provide ongoing training programs that are designed to keep our employees informed of our Privacy Principles.Access:At Adventure Rabbi, Inc., you have access to your registration information. Please send an email inquiry to info@adventurerabbi.com.Children’s Policy:At Adventure Rabbi, Inc., we believe that parents own their children’s personal data. We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13. In the event Adventure Rabbi, Inc. learns that a registrant is under age 13, we will take steps to ensure that that registrant’s information is deleted from our database. We encourage parents to actively participate in their children’s activities on the Internet and to educate children on the safe use of this exciting new medium.Accountability:Adventure Rabbi, Inc. takes our responsibility to manage your information and protect your privacy very seriously. We have made the commitment to have our Privacy Policies and Practices audited by independent organizations.Because we are committed to your privacy and value your trust, this site has agreed to notify you of the following:What personally identifiable information of yours is collectedWhat organization is collecting the informationHow the information is usedWith whom the information may be sharedWhat choices are available to you regarding the collection, use, and distribution of the informationWhat type of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of information under the company’s controlHow you can correct any inaccuracies in the informationIf you have questions or concerns regarding this site’s privacy statement, please contact us:
info@adventurerabbi.com.Returns and Refunds PolicyThank you for your purchase at Adventure Rabbi.Please read this policy carefully. This is the Return and Refund Policy of Adventure Rabbi.All payments to Adventure Rabbi, unless specifically noted on the registration page, are non-refundable.Registration Fees are non-refundable, but are transferable to another person attending the same event in the same year.Contact usIf you have any questions about our Returns and Refunds Policy, please contact us:By phone: 303.417.6200By email: info@adventurerabbi.orgContact Adventure RabbiName*
First
Last
Email*
Phone*Comments
Adventure RabbiThe Mock Building
825 South Broadway St #10
Boulder, CO 80305303.443.2642
info@adventurerabbi.org
Copyright © 2001-2020, Adventure Rabbi: Synagogue w/o Walls. All Rights Reserved. Privacy Policy | Refund Policy Adventure Rabbi
4.85 out of 5 based on 71 ratings. 18 user reviews.
